{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "In word zero of the counter element , bit 14 represents ________.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "CU bit",
        "b": "CD bit",
        "c": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct addressing format of counter’s status bit (Done bit). ",
      "answers": {
        "a": "C5:14.DN",
        "b": "C5:14.dn",
        "c": "C5:14/dn",
        "d": "C5:14/DN"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct addressing format of counter’s status bit (Count- up-enable-bit).",
      "answers": {
        "a": "C5:12.CU",
        "b": "C5:12/CU",
        "c": "C5:12-CU",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "A counter instruction is an __________ .",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Input instruction",
        "b": "Both Input instruction and output instruction",
        "c": "Output instruction"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Consider 2 statements<br><u>Statement 1</u> - The counter will retain its accumulated value through a power loss.<br><u>Statement 2</u> - The counter will retain the ON or OFF status of done bit ,overflow bit and underflow bits through a power loss.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Statement 1 is true",
        "b": "Statement 2 is true",
        "c": "Both Statement 1 and Statement 2 is true"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Everytime the count-up instruction sees a false-to-true rung transition, a count-up counter‘s accumulated value is _______.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Decremented by one",
        "b": "Incremented by one"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "For a count-up counter, in the event of wrap from +32,767 to -32,768, the accumulated value becomes less than the preset value and the done bit will ___________.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "not be reset",
        "b": "be reset"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "In the word zero, of the counter element, _______ bit is set when the accumulated value of a count-up counter has reached the highest possible accumulated value, which is +32,767. At This point, the counter will automatically wrap around and start counting up from the maximum negative value -32,768.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Bit 10",
        "b": "Bit 11",
        "c": "Bit 12",
        "d": "Bit 13"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "In default counter file, how to address the counter’s 16 accumulated value?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "C5:16/ACC",
        "b": "C5:ACC/16",
        "c": "C16:5.ACC",
        "d": "C5:16-ACC"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "_________ is the current (r.m.s value) that a Circuit breaker is capable of breaking under specified conditions and given recovery voltage.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "C5:16.PRE",
        "b": "C5:16/PRE",
        "c": "C16:5/PRE",
        "d": "C16:5.PRE"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": ""
    }
  ]
}
